let questions = [
    {
        question:"What does HTML stand for?",
        choice:["Hyper Trainer Marking Language", "Hyper Text Marketing Language", "Hyper Text Markup Language", "Hyper Text Markup Leveler"],
        answer:"Hyper Text Markup Language"
    },
    {
        question:"<h1>Text</h1> is the correct way of making a header in HTML.",
        choice:["True", "False"],
        answer:"True"
    },
    {
        question:"The Tag is used To Give Heading To The Table.",
        choice:["Head", "Td", "Th", "Caption"],
        answer:"Head"
    },
    {
        question:"What type of function is used to parse a string to Int:?",
        choice:["Integer.Parse", "Int.Parse", "Parse.Int", "None"],
        answer:"Parse.Int"
    },
    {
        question:"A Function Associated With An object is Called:",
        choice:["Function", "Method", "Link", "None"],
        answer:"Method"
    },
    {
        question:"If button is clicked... event handler is invoked.",
        choice:["OnSubmit()", "OnLoad()", "IsPostBack()", "OnClick()"],
        answer:"OnClick()"
    },
    {
        question:"IsNaN() Evaluates And Argument To Determine if Given Value:",
        choice:["Is not a null","Is not a number","Is not a new object","None of the above"],
        answer:"Is not a number"
    },
    {
        question:"JavaScript File has an extension of:",
        choice:[".Java",".Js",".javascript",".xml"],
        answer:".Js"
    },
    {
        question:"Event used to check an empty text box:",
        choice:["OnClick()","OnFocus()","OnBlur()","None"],
        answer:"OnBlur()"
    },
    {
        question:"GetMonth() returns the month as:",
        choice:["Int","Float","Char","String"],
        answer:"Int"
    },
    {
        question:"Method Prompt() contain ___ number of parameters",
        choice:['One','Two','Three','Zero'],
        answer:"Two"
    }
];